reject reasonable projects due to personal feelings
nor will I use personal ties
to accept projects with unclear risks
Will you still come back in the future
If it's just for dinner
I will consider it
But if you want me to
deal with Su Yurou's emotions
handle the Gu family's pressure for the Su family
or make me compromise
I won't come
Okay Mingyao
At the Su Group I want to
reserve a position for you
It's not to make you serve the Su family
It's just that you are truly capable
Your judgment on contracts and projects
is better than I expected
If there are suitable projects in the future
I can participate as a professional
But not as a way to compensate your daughter
Nor as a bridge to the Fu Group
Alright
You can get to know me again
But stop trying to dictate who I am
Ah
Feeling sad
Yes
A little but mostly I feel relieved
They are willing to get to know me again
I can give them a chance
But my life
no longer needs their approval